adityabirla.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy and cookies policy - Aditya Birla Group

The Aditya Birla Management Corporation Private Ltd (ABMCPL) has adopted the following Privacy Policy, which is applicable to all personally identifiable information that you provide to ABMCPL through www.adityabirla.com (the "Website") or for purposes of using the Website. 

You must also review and accept our Website Terms of Use as it is also applicable and govern your use of the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any personally identifiable information that you may provide to third parties, such as through other sites linked to the Website. Please be aware that if you choose to visit such third party sites, you should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies because that third party's privacy policy, and not our Website's, will govern your activities and any personally identifiable information you disclose while visiting the third party site.

ABMCPL expressly reserves its sole discretion, and at times and intervals of its choosing the right to change this Privacy Policy periodically in the future without prior notice to the users. User shall review our Privacy Policy available at the Website regularly to be sure you are fully current with our practices and procedures in this area. Your continued use of the Website will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Website:

**Overview**  
As part of the normal operation of the Website, we collect and, in some cases, may disclose personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the personally identifiable information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.

By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Terms of Use and governs all use of the Website.

We may collect your name, address, email address, telephone number, and other personally identifiable information you submit on the Website. Such personally identifiable information will not be posted in areas of the Website viewable by the public or users of the Site.

**Our Use of Your Information**  
Our primary goal in collecting personally identifiable information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that are most likely to meet your needs, and to customize the Website and our services to make your experience easier. We use personally identifiable information in the files we maintain about you, and the other personally identifiable information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Website to provide you with services.

**Use of Cookies**   
This website may place and access certain Cookies on your computer and uses them to improve your experience of using the Website.

Before the website places cookies on your computer, you will be presented with a message bar requesting your consent to set those Cookies. You may, if you wish, deny consent to the placing of Cookies; however certain features of the Website may not function fully or as-intended.

You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. By default, most internet browsers accept Cookies, but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet browser.

This Website may place the following Cookies:

**Type of Cookie** | **Purpose**  
---|---  
jquery.cookie | Saves your chat history while you use the ABG Site Assistant. This ensures that your experience across the website is seamless  
_utma, _utmb, _utmc, _utmz,display_features_cookie | Google Analytics is used on the Websites to track visitor traffic and site performance traffic by collecting anonymous information about the average time spent on the website, the pages viewed and other relevant usage statistics. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics visit: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>   
  
**Our Disclosure of Your Information**  
Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be required to disclose personally identifiable information to the government, law enforcement agencies, or third parties under certain circumstances; third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications; or users or authorized users may independently abuse or misuse your information that they collect from the Website in violation of our Website's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. Therefore, although we use industry standard information security practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed. 

Advertisers: We may aggregate (gather data across all Authorized Users) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. 

Other Corporate Entities: We may sometimes share data with our affiliates, subsidiaries, joint ventures and third party service providers that provide us with services and/or provide you with services. To the extent that these entities have access to your personally identifiable information, we will ask them to treat it at least as protectively as they treat personally identifiable information they obtain from their other authorized users or members. Our affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures will follow privacy practices no less protective of all authorized users and members than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. It is possible that ABMCPL, its subsidiaries, affiliates, joint ventures or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that ABMCPL would share some or all of your personally identifiable information in order to continue to maintain and provide access to the Website. 

Legal Requests: ABMCPL co-operates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws relating to matters, such as intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorise us to) disclose any personally identifiable information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe reasonably necessary or appropriate, in connection with any investigation.

**Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
We will, however, retain in our files and databases personally identifiable information you have requested to remove in order to use it in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior personally identifiable information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back up" systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

**Security**  
ABMCPL may use reasonable security measures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as "firewalls," Secure Socket Layers (SSL), and other physical and electronic security measures. However, you agree and acknowledge that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

**Questions and updates**  
If you have any questions or suggestions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at 

Dr. (Mrs.) Pragnya Ram   
Group executive President - Corporate Communications & CSR  
Aditya Birla Management Corporation Pvt. Ltd.,   
Aditya Birla Centre, 'C' Wing, 1st Floor  
S. K. Ahire Marg, Worli,   
Mumbai – 400 030, India.  
Email: pragnya.ram@adityabirla.com  
Telephone: +91 22 26655160 / 24995160   
Fax: +91 22 66525741 / 24995741
